Eli Gertzman

Email: eligerzman@gmail.com Phone: 0547281982 Address: Tel Aviv

GitHub: https://github.com/EliGertz94 Website: https://elidev.netlify.app/

Full Stack Developer

Fullstack developer with 1 year of experience in professional software development and an ability to adapt and acquire new skills. Achieved proficiency in Java, Spring Framework, Javascript, React, Node.js, Next js ,Microservices, REST APIs, Html, Tailwind CSS, SQL and NoSQL (MongoDB). Have a high level of motivation to learn, Independent, adapt, and take responsibility.

WORK EXPERIENCE

OPEN SOURCE

(Aug 2023 - Now)

Full Stack Developer

- fixed various bugs in different projects and suggested and added wanted features
- Ability to jump into large code bases and able to contribute to projects without guidance
- Learned to work with a team and contribute at the same time

Metrix (System Specialist)

(Aug 2021 - Now)

- Managing cisco network configurations.
- Creating scripts for automation and optimization of the workflow.

EDUCATION

Open University (Apr 2023 - now)

• Computer science Degree

John Bryce, Tel Aviv (Dec 2022 - Aug 2023)

- Completed an intensive course covering Java, Spring, and React.
- Expanded skills beyond the course curriculum to include Node.js.

PROJECTS

• E-commerce site - A front online gadget store for users and admin dashboard to add products to the store. Built with next.js, used mongoDB, NextAuth.js, stripe, typescript.